Guide to the George Dudley Seymour Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Family Genealogy, 1709-1943; Series II; 6.75; (17 boxes)
  - Photographs
    - Seymour, Moses (Box 50, Folder 668)
    - Seymour, Ralph Cowles: daguerreotypes (Box 50, Folder 669)
    - Seymour, Roswell (Box 50, Folder 670)
    - Seymour, William H. (Box 50, Folder 671)
    - Seymour family
      - Description of photographs (Box 50, Folder 672)
      - Headstones (Box 50, Folder 673)
      - House: Hartford, Connecticut (Box 51, Folder 674-675)
      - Portraits(paintings) (Box 51, Folder 676)
      - Unidentified and miscellanea (Box 51, Folder 677-679)
    - Watson, Royal Isaac (Box 51, Folder 680)
    - Welles, Roger (Box 51, Folder 681)
    - Welles family (Box 51, Folder 682)
    - Unidentified and miscellanea
      - Children (Box 52, Folder 683)
      - Men (Box 52, Folder 684-685)
      - Women (Box 52, Folder 686-687)
      - Groups (Box 52, Folder 688)
- Nathan Hale, 1701-1948; Series III; 9.5; (24 boxes)
  This series contains correspondence, research materials, photographs, printed material, clippings and miscellanea relating to Seymour's antiquarian and literary interests in Nathan Hale.
  The series is arranged in the following sections:
  General correspondence
  Select correspondence
  Associates and friends
  Biography
  Birthplace
  Celebrations and tributes
  Coventry, Connecticut
  Documentary Life of Nathan Hale
  Family
  Hale and Wyllys
  Manuscripts
  Memorabilia
  Memorials and monuments
  Military life
  Paltsits, Victor Hugo
  Personal appearance
  Personal life
  Postage stamp
  Miscellaneous
  - General correspondence
    - 1912-1940, undated (Box 53, Folder 689-695)
  - Select correspondence
    - Jacobus, Donald Lines, 1929-1940 (Box 53, Folder 696)
      See also: box 16, folder 154-155 See also: box 41, folder 496-498 See also: box 66, folder 933
    - Johnston, Henry Phelps, 1907-1922 (Box 53, Folder 697-700)
    - Paltsits, Victor Hugo, 1907-1943 (Box 53, Folder 701-704)
      See also: box 73, folder 1084 See also: box 74, folder 1097
    - Strickland, Emily, 1914-1926 undated (Box 53, Folder 705-708)
      See also: box 28, folder 274
  - Associates and friends
    - General correspondence and research material, 1913-1940, undated (Box 54, Folder 709-718)
    - Select correspondence and research material
      - Andre, John, 1834-1936, undated (Box 54, Folder 719-726)
      - Bostwick, Elisha, 1915-1920s, undated (Box 54, Folder 727-728)
      - Christopher family, 1915-1926 (Box 54, Folder 729)
      - Dwight, Timothy, 1812, 1914-1930, undated (Box 54, Folder 730)
      - "Figures on the Stage of the Hall Drama", undated (Box 55, Folder 731-734)
      - Fitch, Eleazar, 1765 (Box 55, Folder 735)
      - Green family, 1926-1930 (Box 55, Folder 736)
      - Gridley family, 1918-1926, undated (Box 55, Folder 737)
      - H[underline], P[underline], [ca1942] (Box 55, Folder 738-739)
      - Hallam, John G. and Lydia, 1923-1928, undated (Box 55, Folder 740)
      - Hamilton, Alexander, undated (Box 55, Folder 741)
      - Hempstead, Steven and family, 1797, [ca1930s] (Box 55, Folder 741)
      - Hillhouse, James, 1810, 1924-1930s, undated (Box 55, Folder 742)
      - Howe, William (Sir), 1925 (Box 55, Folder 742)
      - Hubbard, Polly, 1922-1924 (Box 55, Folder 743)
      - Hull, William, 1805, 1925, undated (Box 55, Folder 743)
      - Huntington, Sam and Joseph, 1776, 1917-1929 (Box 55, Folder 743)
      - Hurlburts, George, 1775-1776 (Box 55, Folder 744)
      - Knowlton, Thomas, 1930 (Box 55, Folder 745)
      - Lafayette, Marquis de, undated (Box 55, Folder 745)
      - Latimer, Robert, 1913-1921, undated (Box 55, Folder 745)
      - Little, William, 1776 (Box 55, Folder 746)
      - Mackenzie, Fred, undated (Box 55, Folder 746)
      - Marvin, Elihu, 1770s, 1914-1936 (Box 55, Folder 747)
      - Mead, J. L., 1922 (Box 55, Folder 747)
      - Montresor, John (Captain) (Box 55, Folder 748-749)
      - Munson, Aeneas, [ca1920] (Box 55, Folder 750)
      - Munson, Eneas, 1772 (Box 55, Folder 750)
      - Ripley, Alice Adams
        - General correspondence, 1924-1940 (Box 56, Folder 751-754)
        - Research materials, [ca1910-1930s] (Box 56, Folder 755-758)
        - Select correspondence
          - Paltsits, Victor Hugo, 1914-1925 (Box 56, Folder 759)
          - Ripley, Laura Maria, 1915-1920 (Box 56, Folder 760)
          - Shriver, Isabel Hastings, undated (Box 56, Folder 761)
            See also: box 73, folder 1077
      - Robinson, William, 1773 (Box 56, Folder 762)
      - Saltonstall, Gilbert, 1775 (Box 56, Folder 763)
      - Seldon, Ezra, 1928, undated (Box 56, Folder 764)
      - Sill, Richard, 1924-1935, undated (Box 56, Folder 765)
      - Talmadge, Benjamin, 1914-1929, undated (Box 56, Folder 766)
      - Updike, Thomas F., 1775 (Box 56, Folder 767)
      - Washington, George (photocopies), 1782, 1912-1932 (Box 56, Folder 767)
      - Webb, Charles, [ca1770] (Box 56, Folder 768)
      - Williams, Ebenezer, [ca1775], 1916-1939, undated (Box 56, Folder 769)
      - Wright, Asher, 1919-1939, undated (Box 56, Folder 770)
      - Wyllys, George and Pitkin, John, 1756 (Box 56, Folder 771)
  - Biography
    - General correspondence and miscellanea, 1914-1943, undated (Box 57, Folder 772-777)
    - Select correspondence and research materials
      - Adams, Hannah, [ca1929] (Box 57, Folder 778)
      - Bradley, Cyrus Parker, 1835-1837, 1928 (Box 57, Folder 779)
        See also: box 57, folder 783-785
      - Clements, William L., 1933 (Box 57, Folder 780)
      - Crofut, Florence S., 1932 (Box 57, Folder 781)
      - Fristie, Ellen Morgan, 1914-1915 (Box 57, Folder 782)
      - Gilbert, Jasper and Bradley, Cyrus Parker, 1834-1837, 1920s (Box 57, Folder 783-785)
      - Hoadley, George E., 1911-1920s (Box 57, Folder 786-788)
      - Johnston, H. P., undated (Box 57, Folder 789)
      - Root, Jean Christie, 1913-1915, undated (Box 57, Folder 790-794)
      - Schoolbooks and texts, 1922-1923 (Box 57, Folder 795)
      - Sprague, William Buel, 1918-1945 (Box 57, Folder 796)
      - Stuart papers, 1933-1940, undated (Box 57, Folder 797)
      - Tallman, S. H., 1930-1932, undated (Box 57, Folder 798)
  - Birthplace
    - General correspondence and research material, 1913-1943, undated (Box 58, Folder 799-816)
    - Architecture
      See also:box 118, folder 1
    - Caretakers
      - General, 1915-1927, 1941-1942 (Box 59, Folder 826)
      - Gifford, Etta Mae, 1937-1944 (Box 59, Folder 827)
      - Graves, Henry Solon, 1942-1943, undated (Box 60, Folder 828-830)
        See also: box 12, folder 114-118 See also: box 88, folder 1297
      - Griffith, Harold, 1927-1942 (Box 60, Folder 831-834)
        See also: box 13, folder 120
      - Griffith, Mary Elizabeth, 1940-1941 (Box 60, Folder 835)
      - Griffith, William H., 1925-1930 (Box 60, Folder 836-837)
      - Lord, W. S., 1915-1916 (Box 60, Folder 838)
    - Exterior details
      - Farm products and animals, 1917-1919, undated (Box 60, Folder 839)
      - Fire protection, 1927 (Box 60, Folder 840)
      - Geology, 1927 (Box 60, Folder 841)
      - Maps: plots of land, 1916, 1935 (Box 60, Folder 842)
      - Miscellaneous, 1938-1942 (Box 60, Folder 843)
      - Roads, 1923, 1932-1936 (Box 60, Folder 844)
      - Taxes, 1916, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 845)
      - Timber, 1915-1939, undated (Box 60, Folder 846)
      - Tower, 1928-1931 (Box 60, Folder 847)
      - Walls, water and well, 1915-1939 (Box 60, Folder 848)
    - Furnishings
      - General, 1914-1934 (Box 61, Folder 849)
      - Coffins and hardware, 1929, undated (Box 61, Folder 850)
      - Inventories: vols. I, II, and misc., [ca1915-1942, undated] (Box 61, Folder 851-858)
      - Portraits and bookplate, 1926, undated (Box 61, Folder 859)
      - Silver, 1942, undated (Box 61, Folder 860)
      - Stores, 1908-1943 (Box 61, Folder 861)
    - Photographs
      - Exteriors, undated (Box 61, Folder 862)
      - Interiors, undated (Box 61, Folder 863)
      - Scrapbook pages, undated (Box 62, Folder 864)
      - Tombstones and miscellaneous, undated (Box 62, Folder 865)
    - Purchase and disposition
      - General, 1913-1925, undated (Box 62, Folder 866-868)
      - Abstracts of title, 1910s (Box 62, Folder 869)
      - Congratulations, 1912-1915 (Box 62, Folder 870)
      - Contract for construction, undated (Box 62, Folder 871)
      - Management, 1940-1941 (Box 62, Folder 872)
      - National monument, 1941-1943, undated (Box 62, Folder 873-875)
      - Newspaper articles and research, 1913-1914, 1942, undated (Box 62, Folder 876)
    - Souvenirs
      - Scrapbook: Hale relatives, vols. I & II, undated (Box 63, Folder 877-880)
  - Celebrations and tributes
    - Birthday, 1923-1929 (Box 64, Folder 881)
    - Dramas, 1844-1941 (Box 64, Folder 882-887)
    - Fame, 1925-1928 (Box 64, Folder 888)
    - History of tributes, 1914-1928, undated (Box 64, Folder 889)
    - Map, 1931-1935 (Box 64, Folder 890)
    - Movie, 1916-1925 (Box 64, Folder 891)
    - Name: commercialized, used for organizations, 1924-1926 (Box 64, Folder 892-893)
    - Pageants: New London, 1926, 1931, 1935 (Box 64, Folder 894)
      See also: box 64, folder 908-910
    - Poetry, 1836, 1907-1933 (Box 64, Folder 895-898)
    - Schools, 1925, 1933 (Box 64, Folder 899)
    - Sesquecentennial celebration, 1926, undated (Box 64, Folder 900-903)
    - South Coventry, Connecticut, 1926 (Box 64, Folder 904-905)
    - Willis, Nathaniel: typescript, 1781 (Box 64, Folder 906)
    - Yale Bicentennial, 1901 (Box 64, Folder 907)
    - Yale Pageant, 1916 (Box 64, Folder 908-910)
  - Coventry, Connecticut
    - General correspondence and research materials, 1916-1933, undated (Box 65, Folder 911-914)
    - Cemetery: Ripley plot, 1922 (Box 65, Folder 915)
    - Churches
      - General, 1913-1932, undated (Box 65, Folder 916-917)
      - Essays and research materials, undated (Box 65, Folder 918-921)
    - Doorman house(Nelson place), 1941 (Box 65, Folder 922)
    - Howard house, undated (Box 65, Folder 923)
    - Huntington-Lord house, 1935-1937, 1939 (Box 65, Folder 924)
    - Land, 1918-1936 (Box 65, Folder 925)
    - Land purchases, 1917-1931 (Box 65, Folder 926)
    - Northampton(Strong-Porter)house, 1917-1943 (Box 65, Folder 927)
      See also: box 118, folder 2
    - Schoolhouse, 1931 (Box 65, Folder 928)
    - Taxlists, 1913-1943 (Box 65, Folder 929)
  - Documentary Life of Nathan Hale
    - General, 1918-1936, undated (Box 66, Folder 930)
    - Collier's, 1914-1916 (Box 66, Folder 931)
    - Gifts of writings, 1922-1931, 1941 (Box 66, Folder 932)
    - Jacobus, Donald Lines, 1940-1941, undated (Box 66, Folder 933)
      See also: box 16, folder 154-155 See also: box 41, folder 496-498 See also: box 53, folder 696
    - Illustrations, undated (Box 66, Folder 934-935)
    - LaGuardia, Fiorello Henry, 1943 (Box 66, Folder 936)
    - Publication, 1940-1941, undated (Box 66, Folder 937-938)
    - Schools, 1925-1935 (Box 66, Folder 939)
    - Seymour writings on Hale, undated (Box 66, Folder 940)
    - Reviews, 1934 (Box 66, Folder 941)
  - Family
    - General, 1913-1937, undated (Box 67, Folder 942-944)
    - Buildings, 1924 (Box 67, Folder 945)
    - Genealogy
      - Ancestral tablets, undated (Box 67, Folder 946)
      - Research materials, 1882, 1923-1931, undated (Box 67, Folder 947)
      - Schackford, S. B., 1920-1935, undated (Box 67, Folder 948-949)
    - Individuals
      - Abbott, Hale Rebeckah, 1896, 1931, undated (Box 67, Folder 950)
      - Hale, Arthur, 1925-1941 (Box 67, Folder 951)
      - Hale, David, 1918-1926, undated (Box 67, Folder 952)
      - Hale, Enoch, 1804, 1914-1940, undated (Box 67, Folder 953)
      - Hale, Hannah: to Hale, Nancy, 1802 (Box 67, Folder 954)
      - Hale, John
        - General, 1914, 1926 (Box 67, Folder 955)
        - First Society in Coventry: Abbot, Abiel, 1795 (Box 67, Folder 956)
        - Portrait, 1922-1927, undated (Box 67, Folder 957)
        - Records as Justice of the Peace, 1787, 1796, 1799 (Box 67, Folder 958)
      - Hale, John Strong, undated (Box 67, Folder 959)
      - Hale, Lydia Austin, 1931, undated (Box 67, Folder 960)
      - Hale, Lydia Devan, 1846, 1918 (Box 67, Folder 961)
      - Hale, Nancy (Box 67, Folder 961)
        See: box 67, folder 954
      - Hale, Nathan, 1926-1929 (Box 67, Folder 962)
      - Hale, Richard, 1761-1780, 1799, 1913-1943, undated (Box 67, Folder 963-965)
      - Hale, Richard W., 1926-1927 (Box 67, Folder 966)
      - Hale, Samuel, 1924, undated (Box 67, Folder 967)
      - Hale, William, 1804, undated (Box 67, Folder 968)
      - Hamm, Elizabeth Hale, 1941-1942 (Box 67, Folder 969)
      - Howard, Chauncy
        - Beecher, Henry Ward, 1833 (Box 67, Folder 970)
        - Boynton, John W., 1837 (Box 67, Folder 971)
        - Bradley, Cyrus P., 1837 (Box 67, Folder 972)
        - Hale, Mary, 1838 (Box 67, Folder 973)
        - Howard, John Ripley, 1837 (Box 67, Folder 974)
        - Hubbard, Richard (Governor), 1866 (Box 67, Folder 975)
        - Mitchell, N. (?) A., 1858 (Box 67, Folder 976)
      - Howard, John Ripley: Watrous (?), Hattie, undated (Box 67, Folder 977)
      - Howard, Nathan
        - Abbott family, 1804, 1825 (Box 67, Folder 978)
        - Hale, David, 1807-1830 (Box 67, Folder 979)
        - Hale, Enoch, 1804, 1829-1831 (Box 67, Folder 980)
        - Hale, Joanna, 1790 (Box 67, Folder 981)
        - Howard, Chauncey, undated (Box 67, Folder 982-983)
        - Howard, John, 1798, 1804 (Box 67, Folder 984-985)
        - Judson, Andrew J., 1830, 1835-1836 (Box 67, Folder 986)
        - Papers: Justice of the Peace, 1803, 1806 (Box 68, Folder 987)
        - Papers: Nathan Hale execution, n. d. (Box 68, Folder 988)
      - Noyes, James (Rev.), 1701 (Box 68, Folder 989)
      - Plumer, Sally Hale, 1919-1937 (Box 68, Folder 990)
      - Rose, Nathan Hale, 1827 (Box 68, Folder 991)
      - Strong, Joseph: deed, 1733 (Box 68, Folder 992)
      - Strong family, 1940, undated (Box 68, Folder 993)
    - Portraits, 1836, 1921-1926, undated (Box 68, Folder 994)
    - Miscellaneous research material, undated (Box 68, Folder 995)
  - Hale and Wyllys
    - General, 1913-1938, undated (Box 68, Folder 996)
    - Acknowledgements of receipts, 1931-1940, undated (Box 68, Folder 997-998)
    - Charter: Connecticut Charter and Charter Oak, 1931-1933, undated (Box 68, Folder 999-1001)
    - "A Connecticut Soldier in Ohio", undated (Box 68, Folder 1002)
    - Cutler, Manasseh, undated (Box 68, Folder 1003)
    - Illustrations, 1932-1933 (Box 68, Folder 1004)
    - Publication data, 1930-1933 (Box 68, Folder 1005)
    - Reviews, 1933-1935 (Box 68, Folder 1006-1007)
    - Sale of book, undated (Box 68, Folder 1008)
    - Wyllys family
      - General, 1931-1937, undated (Box 69, Folder 1009-1014)
      - Alsop, Richard, 1934, undated (Box 69, Folder 1015)
      - Lee, Antis, 1931-1932 (Box 69, Folder 1016)
      - Pomeroy, Mary Wyllys, 1806, 1928, 1934 (Box 69, Folder 1017)
      - Wyllys: brazier, 1931 (Box 69, Folder 1018)
      - Wyllys: house, 1931-1934, undated (Box 69, Folder 1019)
      - Wyllys, George, 1932, undated (Box 69, Folder 1020)
      - Wyllys, Ralph, 1932, undated (Box 69, Folder 1021)
      - Wyllys, Ruth, 1902, 1910 (Box 69, Folder 1022)
      - Wyllys, Samuel, undated (Box 69, Folder 1023)
    - Miscellaneous research material, undated (Box 69, Folder 1024)
  - Manuscripts
    - General, 1912-1939 (Box 69, Folder 1025-1026)
    - Camp book, 1921 (Box 69, Folder 1027)
    - Commission, 1918-1940, undated (Box 69, Folder 1028)
    - Hale, Enoch: letters of 1776, 1925 (Box 69, Folder 1029)
    - Military pass, 1915 (Box 69, Folder 1030)
    - Poems, 1916-1934, undated (Box 69, Folder 1031)
    - Poems: typescript: and clippings, Circa 1845-1935 (Box 69, Folder 1032)
    - Poems: Adams, Alicia, 1924-1926, undated (Box 69, Folder 1033)
    - Sales catalogues, 1916, 1926 (Box 70, Folder 1034)
    - Yale University gifts, 1942 (Box 70, Folder 1035)
  - Memorabilia
    - General, 1914-1942, undated (Box 70, Folder 1036)
    - Lists, 1918 (Box 70, Folder 1037)
  - Memorials and monuments
    - General, 1914-1931, undated (Box 70, Folder 1038)
    - Austin, Henry, 1846-1847 (Box 70, Folder 1039)
      See also: box 118, folder 1
    - Brooklyn Heights: Brother Jonathan, 1846 (Box 70, Folder 1040)
      See also: box 118, folder 4
    - Coventry, Connecticut, 1835-1857, 1916-1917 (Box 70, Folder 1041)
    - Coventry, Connecticut: Votive chapel, 1923-1930 (Box 70, Folder 1042)
    - Fort Hale Park, 1887-1917, 1921-1923, undated (Box 70, Folder 1043-1045)
    - Government documents, 1836-1840 (Box 70, Folder 1046)
    - Hall of Fame, New York University, 1920 (Box 70, Folder 1047)
    - Nathan Hale Memorial, 1916-1918, 1929-1935, undated (Box 70, Folder 1048)
    - Printed material, 1845-1926 (Box 71, Folder 1049)
    - South Coventry Church, 1922-1926, 1931-1934 (Box 71, Folder 1050)
    - Statues
      - General, 1907-1934 (Box 71, Folder 1051)
      - Gerhardt,[underline], 1924-1928 (Box 71, Folder 1052)
      - MacMonnies, Frederick W., 1934-1935 (Box 71, Folder 1053)
      - Nathan Hale Statue Committee, 1899-1915 (Box 71, Folder 1054-1055)
      - Pratt, Bela Lyon
        - General, 1899-1936 (Box 71, Folder 1056-1057)
        - Clippings, 1934 (Box 71, Folder 1058)
        - Gift of photos, 1917-1936 (Box 71, Folder 1059-1060)
        - Lettering, 1907 (Box 71, Folder 1061)
        - Photographs, undated (Box 71, Folder 1062)
        - Replicas, 1922-1948 (Box 71, Folder 1063-1064)
      - Yale University, 1896-1918, undated (Box 72, Folder 1065-1069)
    - Tablet: United States Military Academy, 1935 (Box 72, Folder 1070)
  - Military life
    - Betrayal, 1919-1930, undated (Box 72, Folder 1071-1073)
    - Capture and execution
      - General, 1919-1940, undated (Box 72, Folder 1074-1076)
      - Printed material, 1857, 1920s (Box 73, Folder 1077)
      - Rogers, James Gamble, 1939 (Box 73, Folder 1078)
        See also: box 25, folder 248
      - Stillman, Henry Allyn: "An Aged Witness", 1904 (Box 73, Folder 1079)
    - Death, 1919-1939 (Box 73, Folder 1080)
    - Last words
      - General, 1918-1932, undated (Box 73, Folder 1081)
      - Addison's Cate, 1911-1933 (Box 73, Folder 1082)
    - Trial: location, 1922, undated (Box 73, Folder 1083)
  - Paltsits, Victor Hugo
    - General correspondence, 1894-1901, 1914, 1927, 1935-1946 (Box 73, Folder 1084)
    - Select correspondence: Seymour, George Dudley, 1912-1942 (Box 73, Folder 1085-1086)
    - Associates and friends
      - General, undated (Box 73, Folder 1087)
      - Ripley, Alice Adams, 1897, 1901, undated (Box 73, Folder 1088)
        See also: box 56, folder 760
    - Bibliography, undated (Box 73, Folder 1089)
    - Biography
      - "Life of Nathan Hale, the American Martyr-Spry of the Revolution", 1894 (Box 73, Folder 1090)
      - Other authors, 1910-1923, undated (Box 73, Folder 1091)
      - Research materials, undated (Box 73, Folder 1092-1094)
    - Birthplace, 1914 (Box 73, Folder 1095)
    - Book reviews, 1900-1902 (Box 73, Folder 1096)
    - Books: owned by Hale, 1899-1930 (Box 74, Folder 1097)
    - Bradley, Cyrus Parker: manuscripts and related correspondence, [ca1838-1848] (Box 74, Folder 1098)
    - Burning of New York, 1913 (Box 74, Folder 1099)
    - Celebrations and tributes
      - East Haddam, Connecticut, 1899-1900 (Box 74, Folder 1100-1101)
      - New London, Connecticut, 1896-1901 (Box 74, Folder 1102)
    - Hale, Artemus, [ca1825-1911] (Box 74, Folder 1103)
    - Literature and fiction, 1900-1925 (Box 74, Folder 1104)
    - Manuscripts
      - General, 1894-1901, 1917-1934, undated (Box 74, Folder 1105)
      - Bennett, Fanny Rose, 1934 (Box 74, Folder 1106)
      - Hale, Richard: letters, 1911-1916 (Box 74, Folder 1107)
    - Memorabilia, 1900 (Box 74, Folder 1108)
    - Memorials and monuments, 1899-1927 (Box 74, Folder 1109)
    - Military life
      - Capture, 1894-1941 (Box 74, Folder 1110)
      - Execution, [ca1834-1835, 1898; 1911] (Box 74, Folder 1111-1112)
    - Other Nathan Hales, 1899-1927 (Box 74, Folder 1113)
    - Personal life
      - Teacher, 1894-1899, undated (Box 74, Folder 1114)
      - Yale, 1899-1936 (Box 74, Folder 1115)
  - Personal appearance
    - Bostwick, Elisha: description, 1927-1936, undated (Box 75, Folder 1116)
    - "The Familiar Hale": acknowledgements, 1907-1914 (Box 75, Folder 1117)
    - Shadow portrait, 1914, 1917-1939, undated (Box 75, Folder 1118-1119)
  - Personal life
    - Masonic order, 1925 (Box 75, Folder 1120)
    - New York, 1917-1935, undated (Box 75, Folder 1121)
    - New London, Connecticut, 1920-1934 (Box 75, Folder 1122)
    - Romances
      - General, 1915, 1926-1935, undated (Box 75, Folder 1123)
      - "The Hale Romances": drafts, undated (Box 75, Folder 1124)
    - Teacher, 1924-1939, undated (Box 75, Folder 1125)
    - Yale University, 1912-1940, undated (Box 75, Folder 1126)
  - Postage stamp
    - General and clippings, 1926-1938 (Box 76, Folder 1127-1128)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Clippings, [ca1907-1913] (Box 76, Folder 1129-1130)
- New Haven City Planning, 1835-1935; Series IV; 8; (16 boxes)
  This series contains correspondence, photographs, drawings, printed material, clippings, volumes, and miscellanea relating to Seymour's activities in city planning.
  The series is arranged in two sections: Correspondence and Letterbooks-scrapbooks. Correspondence is arranged alphabetically by the individual, organization, or topic and Letterbook-scrapbooks are arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - Correspondence
    - A (Box 77, Folder 1131)
    - American City, 1909-1914 (Box 77, Folder 1132)
    - American Civic Association, 1907-1916 (Box 77, Folder 1133-1134)
    - American Federation of Arts, 1910-1912 (Box 77, Folder 1135)
    - American Institute of Architects, 1907-1916 (Box 77, Folder 1136)
    - B (Box 77, Folder 1137)
    - Board of Aldermen, 1910-1915, undated (Box 77, Folder 1138)
    - C (Box 77, Folder 1139)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1909-1914 (Box 77, Folder 1140-1143)
    - Chicago Plan Commission, 1911-1915 (Box 77, Folder 1144)
    - City Beautiful, 1910-1921, undated (Box 78, Folder 1145)
    - City Beautiful Committee, 1910, undated (Box 78, Folder 1146)
    - City Charter, 1911, undated (Box 78, Folder 1147)
    - City Plan Commission, 1912-1921 (Box 78, Folder 1148)
    - City planning
      - Clippings, 1912-1924, undated (Box 78, Folder 1149)
        See also: Box 118, folder 5
      - Early towns and cities, 1920-1912, undated (Box 78, Folder 1150)
      - Printed material, 1909-1916 (Box 78, Folder 1151)
      - World War I, 1917-1918 (Box 78, Folder 1152)
    - Civic Federation of New Haven, 1909-1920 (Box 78, Folder 1153)
    - Civic Improvement Committee report acknowledgments, 1911 (Box 79, Folder 1154)
    - D (Box 79, Folder 1155)
    - E (Box 79, Folder 1156)
    - Exhibit of Congestion of Population in New York City, 1907-1910 (Box 79, Folder 1157)
    - F (Box 79, Folder 1158)
    - Farnam, Henry W., 1907-1913, undated (Box 79, Folder 1159)
    - First Municipal Planning Exhibition in America, 1911 (Box 79, Folder 1160)
    - Ford, Frederick L., 1909-1912 (Box 79, Folder 1161)
    - G (Box 79, Folder 1162)
    - Gilbert, Cass, 1907-1914, 1924, 1931 (Box 79, Folder 1163-1166)
      See also: box 11, folder 109 See also: box 94, folder 1375
    - H (Box 79, Folder 1167)
    - Hoggson Brothers, 1908 (Box 79, Folder 1168)
    - I-K (Box 79, Folder 1169)
    - L (Box 80, Folder 1170)
    - Lowrie, Charles N., 1907 (Box 80, Folder 1171)
    - M (Box 80, Folder 1172)
    - Machado, Ernest M. A., 1907 (Box 80, Folder 1173)
    - McKim, Mead, and White, 1907-1909 (Box 80, Folder 1174)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 80, Folder 1175)
    - Municipal Journal and Engineer, 1907 (Box 80, Folder 1176)